var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَبَابِيلَ",
        "answer": "(in) flocks",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "abābīla",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَأْكُولٍ",
        "answer": "eaten up",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "makūlin",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "He make",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "yajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "Then He made them",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalahum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحِجَارَةٍ",
        "answer": "with stones",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "biḥijāratin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "you seen",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "969",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْسَلَ",
        "answer": "And He sent",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "wa-arsala",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْمِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "Striking them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tarmīhim",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِجِّيلٍ",
        "answer": "baked clay",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sijjīlin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "with (the) Companions",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "bi-aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضْلِيلٍ",
        "answer": "astray",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "taḍlīlin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيْرًا",
        "answer": "birds",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ṭayran",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَعَصْفٍ",
        "answer": "like straw",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kaʿaṣfin",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلَ",
        "answer": "dealt",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "faʿala",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفِيلِ",
        "answer": "(of the) Elephant",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-fīli",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their plan",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "kaydahum",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "105",
        "ayah": "1"
    }
]; 
export default words;